Onur Bora Akman

Self-motivated, energetic, and hardworking software development (and cybersecurity minor) student that pertain to current demands. Recognized for discipline, dedication, and responsibility. Extremely capable of resolving problems, learn new technologies and work under pressure. And with the friendly, outgoing personality alongside with the environment experience and familiarity with the society fits the qualifications.

Izmir, Turkey onurboraakman.herokuapp.com onurboraakman@hotmail.com +1(951)406-94-72

in linkedin.com/in/onurborakman

github.com/onurborakman

WORK EXPERIENCE

iLead, Grand Canyon University

Phoenix, AZ · August 2018 - Present

- · Assisted with answering phone call and provided exceptional service to all students
- · Entered details into data system accurately to inform tutor of appointment

Kitchen Help, Panda Express

Phoenix, AZ • January 2020 - March 2020

- · Helped the kitchen team with dishes and cleaning
- · Assisted the kitchen team and cooked food to service
- Restocked the meats and vegetables

Intern, Neuroogle

Izmir, TUR • March 2020 - July 2020

- · Created graphs regarding the customer feedbacks for the software the company provides
- · Assisted the developers of the software the company provides

TECH SKILLS

Vue JS, TypeScript, React JS, PHP, Javascript, Java, MongoDB, MySQL, PostGresql, HTML & CSS, C/C++, C#, ASP.NET, .NET CORE, Unity, Spring Boot, Spring, Laravel, JPA, JDBC, Android Development, Express JS, Angular JS, jQuery, Docker, Kubernetes, REST, XML, AJAX, RabbitMQ, Python, MVC, OOP, Linux, Heroku, Google Cloud Services, Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services, CI/CD, MariaDB, Kanban, Agile Development, Agile Project Management, Scrum, Scrum Management, SQL, NoSQL, Data Structures, Git/Version Control, Github

OTHER SKILLS

Time Management, Teamwork, Ability to Work Under Pressure, Resourcefulness, Hard Working, Adaptability, Attention To Detail, Computer Skills, Planning, Problem Solving, Math Skills, Quick Learner, Able to Lift Heavy Weights, Bilingual (English and Turkish), Statistics, Slack, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Office, Critical Thinking, Data Analysis, Risk Management, Project Lifecycle Management

EDUCATION

Grand Canyon University

Phoenix, AZ • August 2018 — April 2022

B.S. in Software Development and Minor in Cybersecurity GPA: 3.92

CERTIFICATIONS

UDEMY Certificate of Completion - The Complete JavaScript Course 2020: Build Real Projects! August 2020

UDEMY Certificate of Completion - Spring Framework Master Class - Java Spring the Modern Way November 2020

HACKERRANK Java (Basic) Certificate December 2020

SOLOLEARN PHP Course December 2020

HACKERRANK Problem Solving (Basic) Certificate January 2021

UDEMY Certificate of Completion - The Web Developer Bootcamp 2021 May 2021

HACKERRANK CSS Certificate August 2021